vircurex.com 2013-12-21

# Bitcoin, Namecoin, Litecoin, Devcoin, IXCoin, PPCoin, Terracoin, Freicoin, Feathercoin, Primecoin (BTC/NMC/LTC/DVC/I0C/IXC/PPC/TRC/FRC/FTC/XPM) Exchange and Trading Platform

Date of last revision: 30th October 2011

## Introduction

Protecting personally identifying information is a core business value of ours. This privacy statement describes how Vircurex acquires, collects and uses the personally identifying information that you provide or that is generated while using Vircurex's web sites.   
If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or want to contact us regarding how we handle your data, please send an email to customerservice@vircurex.com

## Cookies

We use cookies on our site soley to facilitate the sign up and login process for our services. 

## Information Collected By Our Site

We gather Web server log file information automatically such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to administer our website, to analyze and review possible security threats or misconducton our site. 

## Disclosing personally identifying information

We may also disclose your personally identifying information under the following circumstances only: 

  * as required by law
  * when disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to written government requests to any other third party with your prior consent to do so
  * We do not share your personally identifying information with third parties

## Security

Providing security for the personally identifying information you submit via our site is a priority for us. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to; or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction; of your personally identifying information. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt the transmission of data. Please be aware, however, that no transmission of information via the Internet can be entirely secure. You should, therefore, always use caution when submitting personally identifying information online. 

## Changes to this privace statement

Please note that this privacy statement may change from time to time. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect how we use your personally identifying information, we will advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. We will also post a notice on our web site that this privacy statement has changed.
